<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="character1">Character 1</string>
    <string name="character10">Character 10</string>
    <string name="character2">Character 2</string>
    <string name="character3">Character 3</string>
    <string name="character4">Character 4</string>
    <string name="character5">Character 5</string>
    <string name="character6">Character 6</string>
    <string name="character7">Character 7</string>
    <string name="character8">Character 8</string>
    <string name="character9">Character 9</string>
    <string name="days_app_name">30 Characters</string>
    <string name="himeno">Himeno</string>
    <string name="himeno_desc">
Himeno is a calm, reliable Devil Hunter who hides her pain behind humor. She\'s fiercely loyal and carries deep emotional scars from the job.
</string>
    <string name="maki">Maki</string>
    <string name="maki_desc">
Maki is disciplined, determined, and brutally honest. Despite her lack of cursed energy, she outworks everyone through raw talent, intense training, and unshakable resolve.
</string>
    <string name="makima">Makima</string>
    <string name="makima_desc">
Makima is mysterious, poised, and terrifyingly intelligent. Her calm personality hides ruthless ambition and complete control over every situation around her.
</string>
    <string name="marin">Marin</string>
    <string name="marin_desc">
Marin is cheerful, confident, and full of energy. She loves cosplay, supports others wholeheartedly, and brings brightness into every scene she\'s in.
</string>
    <string name="mikasa">Mikasa</string>
    <string name="mikasa_desc">
Mikasa is quiet, loyal, and incredibly strong. She protects the people she cares about with unmatched focus, discipline, and emotional depth.
</string>
    <string name="mitsuha">Mitsuha</string>
    <string name="mitsuha_desc">
Mitsuha is gentle, kind, and thoughtful. Her life changes through a magical connection, pushing her to grow braver and fight for what matters.
</string>
    <string name="nobara">Nobara</string>
    <string name="nobara_desc">
Nobara is bold, stylish, and straightforward. She balances toughness with genuine compassion, fighting with sharp confidence and a strong sense of identity.
</string>
    <string name="power">Power</string>
    <string name="power_desc">
Power is a chaotic, impulsive Blood Fiend with zero manners but huge confidence. She\'s loud, selfish, hilarious, and unexpectedly protective of those she trusts.
</string>
    <string name="sakura">Sakura</string>
    <string name="sakura_desc">
Sakura grows from an emotional teen into a resilient, intelligent ninja. She\'s strong-willed, compassionate, and determined to protect her friends at any cost.
</string>
    <string name="sakurajima">Sakurajima</string>
    <string name="sakurajima_desc">
Mai Sakurajima is calm, mature, and thoughtful. Despite her fame, she struggles with loneliness and finds comfort in people who genuinely understand her.
</string>
</resources>